# **Eyad Hisham**

I'm a Software Engineer, I worked in many development roles such as developer, business analyst, project manager, product owner and even account manager.

I created many commercial apps in wide variety of platforms/industries/domains.

I have built 6+ commercial mobile apps, 200+ Photoshop scripts and 7+ commercial web systems.

### Contact

Address:

Egypt, cairo, nasr city

Phone:

+20 11 000 99039

Email:

eyadhisham@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ey-ha96

Github:

github.com/xEyad

Portfolio (images)

Online CV

**Technical demos (web):** 

Dynamic widgets builder

Visual pathfinder

## **Technical tool**

- Flutter
- Angular 5+ •
- CSS
- Javascript
- **Typescript**
- Dart
- Node is
- C++ 11
- C++ 14
- AHK
- QT

## Languages

## **Experience**

#### Fabrica dev – software engineer

01/2019 - present

- Designed, developed and deployed <u>connect homes</u> internal web system and mobile app, connect homes is one of major brokers in Egypt. currently holding over 300K leads and works with more than 30+ developers.
- Designed, developed and deployed RE/MAX Egypt internal CRM system that operates and manage the leads coming from the **CAPTOUR** project and distributing it to sub RE/MAX offices/franchises.
- Worked on Waterway internal web system. designed and implemented it's EOI module. Also, built it's mobile app using flutter. "Waterway" is a major realestate developer in Egypt and the solution manages their internal CRM system.
- Worked on Castle developments internal web system, designed and implemented their helpdesk system and built its mobile app that manages their internal CRM and units' reservations using flutter
- Worked on <u>JD Holdings</u> internal web system. This system is used by all 4 major developers under the parent company JD Holdings.
- Built axis internal web system. Axis is realestate broker based on egypt

#### Psycoders – software engineer

01/2020 - present

- Built NewGame e-commerce website. NewGame is boardgames manufcaturer and distributor in egypt.
- Worked on Diet academy web dashboard and built it's **mobile app.** Diet academy is solution that enables users to reserve video or chat packages with the doctor and maintain patient information.
- Worked on Bondo web dashboard and Built it's mobile app. Bondo is a small scale social media that operates over the map, where user can record a voicenote and add some metadata to it, then it will be shown over the google map and other users can interact with it.
- Built Egyptian vets syndicate mobile app.
- Built Venu dine in mobile app

#### **Fiverr - Photoshop Automator**

01/2017 – present

 Successfully created and delivered over 200 photoshop script and automation solutions to 100+ client in more than 16 country

## **Education**

B.Sc. computer science

2013-2017

- Higher technological institute (HTI)
- GPA: 3.0